export const javaQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which keyword is used to define a constant in Java?",
    answer: "C. final",
    options: ["A. const", "B. static", "C. final", "D. immutable"],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "What is the default value of an uninitialized int variable in Java?",
    answer: "A. 0",
    options: ["A. 0", "B. null", "C. undefined", "D. Garbage value"],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which of these is not a primitive data type in Java?",
    answer: "D. String",
    options: ["A. int", "B. double", "C. boolean", "D. String"],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which method is called when an object is created?",
    answer: "B. Constructor",
    options: ["A. init()", "B. Constructor", "C. start()", "D. newObject()"],
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Which access modifier allows a variable to be accessible only within the same class?",
    answer: "A. private",
    options: ["A. private", "B. protected", "C. public", "D. default"],
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which collection type stores elements in key-value pairs?",
    answer: "C. Map",
    options: ["A. List", "B. Set", "C. Map", "D. Queue"],
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Which loop executes at least once, even if the condition is false?",
    answer: "B. do-while",
    options: ["A. for", "B. do-while", "C. while", "D. foreach"],
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which exception is thrown when dividing by zero in Java?",
    answer: "A. ArithmeticException",
    options: [
      "A. ArithmeticException",
      "B. NullPointerException",
      "C. NumberFormatException",
      "D. IllegalArgumentException",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "How can we achieve multiple inheritance in Java?",
    answer: "D. Using interfaces",
    options: [
      "A. Using extends keyword",
      "B. Using abstract classes",
      "C. Using super keyword",
      "D. Using interfaces",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'What will `System.out.println(5 + "5");` output?',
    answer: "C. 55",
    options: ["A. 10", "B. 5 + 5", "C. 55", "D. Compilation error"],
  },
];
